The incredible true story of America's top underdog
Sgt. Stubby: An American Hero is a animation, adventure,
family film directed by Richard Lanni.
The true story of the most decorated dog in American military history -- Sgt.
Stubby -- and the enduring bonds he forged with his
brothers-in-arms in the trenches of World War I.
Robert Conroy (voice), played by Logan Lerman.
Margaret Conroy (voice), played by Helena Bonham Carter.
Gaston Baptiste (voice), played by Gérard Depardieu.
Hans Schroeder / Col. Ty (voice), played by Jim Pharr.
Elmer Olsen / Shopkeeper (voice), played by Jordan Beck.
Sgt. Ray Casburn (voice), played by Jason Ezzell.
Stubby: An American Hero is a 2018 animated adventure film centering on
the real-life Sergeant Stubby, a stray Boston Terrier.
Directed and co-written by Richard Lanni, it features the voices of
Logan Lerman, Helena Bonham Carter and Gérard Depardieu.
The film was released in North America on April 13,
2018, by Fun Academy Motion Pictures.
It received generally positive reviews from critics, who praised it for its "sensitivity and charm",
but was a box office bomb, grossing less than $5 million against its $25 million budget.
The film explores themes of rescue, paris, france, chase, world war i, baseball.